Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana, was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad also possess powers from the devils of the Underworld,
and use them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself and from the support of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
At last, the battle against McGicula and the Spade Kingdom has begun.
After six months of training in the Heart Kingdom, Asta and his friends were ready.
They rescued a group of Spade citizens and took control of an outlying base.
Meanwhile, back in Hajj village where Asta and Yuno grew up, fate arrived in the form of a weakened and weary traveler.
Sir, what happened?
Please, Lord Yuno...
We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world.
Yeah!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world.
To the brand new world!
We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world.
Get your hands up, baby!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world.
Yeah!
They drowned out!
Get it on, get it on,始めよう!
難航不楽のリアリティー
立ち止まる時間はないさ!
Hold on, hold on!
Yeah!
Never be sci-fi for liberty
真実性
乗り込む常識
オブエイ
逆境の先にある朝
Oh, yeah!
幻想に埋もれた人生の夢
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えても
加速してExperience
We can't pay!
Let's go!
Believe in myself
衝動的に突き進め
Don't be afraid
誰よりも高く飛べ
Take it to the sky
想像を超えた世界をこの手に
The ground up
想像せよ
いつはリードない自分の道
Yes! It's a ground up
Hey, yeah!
Believe in myself
Believe in yourself
Hey, yeah!
Yeah!
It's time to die
Where are the children?
I sent them off to school
Seeing this might be a bit frightening for them
Especially the younger ones
Good idea
So, how is he doing?
Sleeping, though not restfully
I used a recovery spell, of course
But his wounds are deep
He may have run into bandits in the forest
This could be a situation that calls for the magic knight's intervention
Yes
Who is he?
The stranger?
Good work!
I'm very proud of you all
Thanks to your efforts
The Spade Kingdom's base in the town of Tolon
Is no longer under the enemy's control
The citizens of the Spade Kingdom
Who were held captive and drained of their mana
To power the mobile fortress are recovering
You saved their lives
I'm still curious why you wanted us to return though
Couldn't we have proceeded further into Spade from there?
Fighting those Stage 2 guys was so boring
I want to go up against someone who's super strong
Remember what we're dealing with here
We can't go barging in without thinking
We need to take time to rest and plan
You're sure the town will be alright without us there to defend it?
Don't worry, we've taken precautions
I asked Noelle to bring one of my clones to Tolon
So the town wouldn't be left vulnerable
Through that clone, I was able to establish a barrier there
Similar to the one that encloses the Heart Kingdom
Having this curse inside of me
Gives the unique advantage of being able to sense the Devil's magic
We've got a variety of weapons at our disposal
Let's use them to gain territory and corner this Devil
Yeah!
Confidence is good
But let's not start acting like this is going to be easy
Alright, that's all I have to say
Still, with Laura Petrka's powers, we might just be able to do it
Even if she is a bit odd
That fight wasn't enough for me
Hey Gazi, you want to go around or two?
Floga's an extremely powerful spirit guardian
And it was an honor to have him as my trainer
But I'd like to see you in action
So please, let me join
Heck yeah! I can come too, right?
The three of you are fresh from the field of battle
You should be resting, not fighting
I'm totally fine! Fresh as a daisy and ready to roll, I swear!
Yeah, and I never say no to the chance for a good bloodbath
Please, don't turn us down! I'm already fired up!
A sparring session sounds like so much fun
Can I come out and play?
What in the world are you thinking, Laura Petrka?
You know you can't do that!
Of course I can! I'm fine!
Ah!
Poor Petrka!
I'm so glad that nobody got injured
Especially since they're all so dumb
They can spar, but I'm still dirty from the battle
What I want is a bath
That sounds wonderful! I'll come!
And you're going with them, young lady
As a queen, you ought to be indulging yourself in a proper bath, not a bloodbath
Oh, right
In that case, I know the perfect place where we can go to relax and get cleaned up
The lovely ladies of the Clover Kingdom bathing with the beautiful queen of the Heart Kingdom?
Bad funeral! No getting hot and bothered over any woman but Lady Sinez!
Stop right there!
Think one more dirty thought and you die
Please, Noelle, I swear! I'm doing everything I can to resist!
Help! We've got trouble! There's danger in the palm frume forest!
A wild Charmy has been sighted!
If we don't do something, she's going to eat every last fruit on the trees!
Not again
Again?
Yeah, uh, Charmy seriously loves the food here
Big surprise, right?
But this is nuts, even for her
Her appetite's been wreaking havoc all over the place
In one forest, she took over a group of monkeys and had them bring her bananas as tribute
And in another, she and a bear threw down over some special apples
Well, to be fair, the fruits of the Heart Kingdom are quite delicious
It must be the pure water
I guess we should go fetch her before things get any more out of hand
I can stop her!
You must be really beat after moving all those people around from place to place
Get some rest, let me handle it
Asta, I'm pretty sure you did more moving than me
But I didn't use magic to do it, so I'm fine!
You can get tired without using magic, but whatever
Go for it!
Good luck!
Please go save our fruit!
Right!
Demon Slayer!
With my new control over anti-magic
I can fly!
I remember when he was just a magicless kid who couldn't fly a broom
Now look at the incredible magic knight he's become
Wow!
How lovely!
Knowledge of this has been passed down through generations
It's the royal family's private spring
Amazing!
I'm honored that you would bring us to such a special place
The mana I'm sensing here is very pure
The spring is fed by El Mora Lake, which has some of the finest water in all of the Heart Kingdom
Bathing here will rejuvenate your skin, leaving it delightfully supple and smooth to the touch
Let's get in!
Agreed!
I feel so much better!
The cold water is nice and refreshing
I forgot to take my glasses off!
Whoops!
You're hopeless
Now then, there's something I've been meaning to ask about for a while
Which one of your girls is dating Asta?
Relationship talk? I'm dying to hear the answer
No, I mean none of us are dating him!
Right! Asta is very kind, not to mention reliable and an absolute gentleman
But now simply isn't the time for that sort of thing
What about when the battle of the Spade Kingdom is over then?
Hello!
Oh my, something tells me you might like that
Although, Nero seems to spend more time with him than anyone else
Yes, why is that? Are you secretly dating him?
It's because his head makes a nice perch
No other reason? No, that's it
So you're interested in the top of his head and nothing else?
Mhm
Well, that's good to know, I suppose
Nero says that now
But they're bound to grow closer the more time they spend together
And then how will she feel?
And what about you, Noelle?
Ah! Ha! Ridiculous! I'd never date an idiot like him!
Oh, I see, that clears things up
Indeed, it does
So, let's talk about your love life, Lorepechka
I've assumed for a while now that you and Gaja were seeing each other, but I wasn't sure
Wait, you thought I was dating him?
I can assure you that's most definitely not the case
Really? But you're always together
You'd make a lovely couple
That is never going to happen
I'm sure Gaja feels the same way
Gaja, you poor man
You'll never hear about this conversation from me, though
This is awesome!
No wonder you're the leader of the Spirit Guardians
Your strength is incredible
Both of you grew surprisingly quickly while you were training here
So this is a good workout for me as well
Just as they have, I too must become stronger
I will protect the Heart Kingdom, even if it costs my life
You and the other magic knights are so nice
I worried you might not be
To be honest, I was a bit intimidated by the prospect of our initial meeting
You were intimidated?
We're the ones who got ambushed when we arrived
Even if it was to check our magic stages
Sorry about that
We understand why it was necessary
And we were thrilled to find out that the Heart Kingdom's ruler is someone as lovely and gracious as you
You're too kind
We could never be as kind as you and everyone we've met since coming here has been to us
I agree
We're all going up against the devil together, so I'm just glad that you're an ally we can trust
Though I can't help wishing you weren't so incredibly clumsy all the time
Noelle?
Yes, well thank you very much for saying that
I'm trying hard to put on a brave face for my people so they can feel confident in their queen despite the troubles we're facing
But it's not easy, and I often fear I'm failing
So it's a comfort to know that there are people like you who I can be honest with about my hopes and my doubts
I guess what I'm trying to say is that I'm happy we became friends
You're so cute, Laura Pechka
Oh come on it's no big deal
No stop, you're gonna make me blush
We feel the same about you
I hope you know that
Woohoo!
This line is so freakin' awesome!
The breeze feels good and it smells all sweet and fruity
Hold on, fruity?
Ha! Gettin' close!
Charmy, you around here somewhere?
Hey, Asta! How's it going?
Did you come for some yummy snack?
Whoa, this has gotten big!
How much have you been eating?
The fruit here is scrubbed idly-uptious.
It would be a crime to let it go to waste.
That's actually what I'm here to talk to you about.
We're worried it might not get the chance.
Oh? So is that why you came here to tell me to stop eating?
Well, yeah, like I said, some of the villagers are worried you and your animals-
Let me tell you something.
Uh?
I don't eat to live, Asta.
No, Charmy Poppinson lives to eat!
One more thing.
Anyone who stands between me and my food will be trampled by sheep
till there's nothing left but their corpse, okay?
Okay, what? Uh, you're joking, right, Charmy?
What's going on over there?
Doesn't that look like?
It's one of Charmy's sheep!
She's totally out of control!
She's gone too far.
Vice Captain, do you have a moment?
Not really?
Is this urgent?
Well, we've received a message from a church in Hajj village.
Tell me at once.
It looks really angry! What are we gonna do?
Did you see that? It's using cotton to gather food!
It could come for ours next!
She's got a whole army of hungry forest creatures backing her up too!
At this rate, all the food in the forest is going to end up in their stomachs!
Oh no. It was my duty to train her, but I created a monster in the process.
So, mana words are like recipes, used to create marvelous dishes of magic.
Which means in order to learn the mana method, I must eat as much as I can.
I can't say I understood her logic.
But I decided to support her.
I recognized Charmy's genius immediately and knew the best thing I could do would be
to eat as much as I can.
I can't say I understood her logic, but I decided to support her.
I recognized Charmy's genius immediately and knew the best thing I could do would be
to help her talent shine even brighter than it already did.
But she did.
Oh no. It was my duty to train her, but I created a monster in the process.
So, mana words are like recipes, used to create marvelous dishes of magic.
Which means in order to learn the mana method, I must eat as much as I can.
I can't say I understood her logic, but I decided to support her.
I recognized Charmy's genius immediately and knew the best thing I could do would be
to help her talent shine even brighter than it already did.
But she fell in love with the food of the Heart Kingdom and before I knew what was happening,
she'd earned a place at the top of the food chain as the forest dominant creature.
And now, it's my job to stop her.
Plant magic! Evergreen Vita Valtoria!
No use. They're going straight through.
Well then.
It's trapped!
Nicely done, Sir Pochop!
No! What if we're next on the menu?
It's still coming.
I thought I was gonna suffocate!
You going to be okay, Asta?
Thanks to you, I appreciate the help!
If we don't act quickly, she'll eat every scrap of the kingdom's food!
Will you work with me to stop Charmy?
You bet I will! Let's do this!
Is there anything in the world better than fruit?
It's yummy, super healthy, mostly made up of water, and thanks to fiber it moves through your system so quickly you never get fooled!
So you're sending your vines against me again, Master?
Sorry, but once let the flames of my hunger become a roaring bonfire that not even you can put out!
Then it's a good thing he's not in this alone!
Huh?
All right!
Ha-ha!
Oh, that's totally not fair!
Fine!
Let's see how you deal with a hole right through the middle of your big gut!
Gotcha, Flood Ball!
So much cotton! I keep cutting and cutting, but it won't stop!
Uh-oh, this is bad!
Even Asta is no match for this opponent.
Will we be stuck watching on the sidelines while she consumes everything?
I'll stop her. Just leave it to me, Potrop.
Charmy, we've been training together side by side for months.
As your friend, I can't allow this gluttonous rampage to continue any longer.
Here, picture magic. Invasion of heat-infused ice!
Woo! I owe you for that, Ryl!
Okay, if we strike while it's frozen, we can take it down!
Let's go, Asta!
Right!
Ah!
They defeated the Charmy!
You saved us!
My trainees have made quite a mess of things.
I am proud to see how much they've grown, though.
What were you thinking, Charmy?
You almost uprooted the whole ecosystem.
Sorry, but the fruit in the Heart Kingdom is so yummy that every bite just left me wanting more.
You totally saved me back there.
I think your paintings have gotten even crazier than they were before.
Yeah, well, training in the Heart Kingdom has been intense, but super fun.
And whenever I think about her, I feel an overwhelming need to create works that rival her beauty.
Wait, who's her?
The sublime goddess who came to my rescue when I was possessed by that elf!
I can feel it!
She's my soulmate!
I'm working as hard as I can, so someday I'll be powerful enough to deserve her.
As a man and a captain.
Not sure if you've noticed, but...
That is 100% Charmy!
What?
That's impossible.
My goddess has a classically athletic figure that captures the artist's eye.
I mean, I know she looks different than you remember, but...
Wow, I've captured some eyes in my time, buddy.
Maybe you haven't noticed, but I'm extremely popular.
How are you still eating?
Is food the only thing you ever think about?
No, you're just being rude, Asta.
Of course I think about stuff that isn't food sometimes.
Something that isn't food.
I wonder how Yuno is doing.
We're almost to Hosh now.
This is like the most boring place ever.
It's finally just the two of us, but there's no way we can have a decent date out here in the middle of nowhere.
I don't know what they need to talk to you about, but when we're done, you're ticking me out for real.
Yuno, are you listening?
Hey, Yuno, hello?
Shut up, Belle.
Good, you're here.
Sister.
I'm sorry to bother you. I know you must be very busy.
Yeah, you know super busy, so let's get a move on, okay?
No, it's fine. What's wrong?
Well, why don't you come inside and I'll explain?
You look just like Queen Ciel. And that necklace. There's no doubt about it.
Who the heck is this guy?
According to him, he came from the Spade Kingdom.
I guess we've got some butt to kick, then.
I swear I am not your enemy.
I know things are different now, but we used to be a peaceful kingdom.
It could be bitterly cold at times, but the people lived happy lives, sheltered by the house of Grin-Burial's warmth.
Then the dark triad appeared. They exiled the Grin-Burial's, and my home became a country ruled by fear.
Lord Yuno, our nation's future is in your hands.
You belong to the royal house of Grin-Burial.
It's Sion, the prince and rightful heir to the Spade Kingdom's throne.
Sion, the prince and rightful heir to the Spade Kingdom.
Beautiful
どんな景色も
君といれば輝くよ
だからずっとそばにいて
And never let go
僕のこの手を
離さないでどこまでも
ついてきて欲しい
The world is so beautiful
Cloverclips
The Ultimate Canvas
I could paint her portrait a million times
Goddess! I long to see you again!
Hey Ril, you know there's a real live Charmy here
you could be painting instead
I'm far too busy trying to get every detail
of the goddess's beauty perfect
The canvas is so soft and smooth
It's almost as if I'm painting on a cloud
When I'm done this may be my ultimate masterpiece
Whoa, that's not a canvas
Finished!
At last my goddess has descended
Wait a minute
How did you not notice where you were painting?
If you eat anymore you're going to stretch my goddess out
For her sake I'm begging you put the bananas down
Ril, be careful
You know what happens to people who stand between me and my food
Aaaah!
Please end this again Charmy
I can't take it!
You're joking right?
You can't be serious about me being the prince of the spade kingdom
I'm very serious
Black Clover page 160
The messenger from the spade kingdom
You are my prince
Aaa!
It was started
You are my prince
Usir
Bentley